Guide to the Whitman College Dean of Students records
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
- Dean of Students, 1946-2015
  - Handbooks, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Health insurance [for International Students], 1987-1993 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Holiday schedules, 1971-1993 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Homecoming [schedules], 1978-1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Honoraries on campus (Phi Beta Kappa, SPURS), 1980-1992 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - IMS [Instructional Media Services], 1990-1993 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Incidents [incident reports, memoranda, petitions], 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2068], 1985-1993 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Incidents [incident reports, memoranda, petitions], 2 of 2 [Partial contents restricted until 2068], 1985-1993 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Incompletes [forms and policies], 1977-1986 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Information distributed to students by others [Financial Aid, Health Center, volunteer opportunities, Outdoor Program], 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Institute of International Education [Partial contents restricted until 2057], 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Insurance for faculty and staff, 1961-1993 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Interim week [schedules of events and memoranda], 1985-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - International Takanawa Insitute, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Intramurals, 1979-1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - "Is Whitman College experimenting?", 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Job descriptions and responsibilities, circa 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Job descriptions and responsibilities, drafting (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Job openings at other colleges [notices of openings, requests for recommendations], 1987-1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Job search procedures [Partial contents restricted until 2060], 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Job search, Assistant Dean of Students [Folder restricted until 2060], 1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Job search, candidate rating sample [Partial contents restricted until 2060], 1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Job search, candidate sample file [Partial contents restricted until 2060], 1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Job search, Dean of Students [Folder restricted until 2069], 1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Job search, Health Center Director [Folder restricted until 2064], 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Job search, sample Coordinator's file [Folder restricted until 2060], 1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Job search, position announcement and job description, Assistant Dean of Students, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Judicial procedure [Partial contents restricted until 2067], 1947, bulk 1984-1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - K [Key request and return procedures], 1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - KWCW [Partial contents restricted until 2060], 1981-1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Langsdorf legal file [Folder restricted until 2068], 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - L.E.A.D. Leadership, encouragement, and development, 1984-1993 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Leadership program, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Leadership training and conference, 1981-1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Legal file, 1 of 3, 1969-1993 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Legal file, 2 of 3, 1969-1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Legal file, 3 of 3, 1969-1993 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Legal liabilities, 1985-1993 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Library (Penrose Memorial), 1978-1993 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - M [Manna, College Media Review], 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Mailings to prospective students, 1948-1953 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - "Mass Communication On Campus," US National Student Association, and memos to faculty, 1958-1982 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - May mailings to freshman, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Meetings [and conferences], 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Memoranda regarding "incidences" on campus, Whitman College Pioneer article on police surveillance, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Memorial Building, 1978-1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Mike Murr scholarship [Partial contents restricted until 2067], 1992 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous (campus) [1987 commencement speech, Under-C Society, Whitman basketball, correspondence and publications], 1976-1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (off-campus) [National On-Campus Report survey, union newsletter, directory of cooperative education programs, various correspondence], 1979-1983 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Motels and hotels in Walla Walla, 1987-1992 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - N [newsletter and seminar information, professional associations], 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - NACUBO [National Association of College and University Business Officers], reports and publications, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - NACUBO [National Association of College and University Business Officers] San Francisco conference materials, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - NASPA [National Association of Student Personnel Administrators], conference materials, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - NASPA [National Association of Student Personnel Administrators]: Mid-level management institutes, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - NASPA [National Association of Student Personnel Administrators]: Mid-level professionals Institute, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - NASPA [National Association of Student Personnel Administrators]: Regions V and VI Visions; "Leadership for the 90's", 1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - News service, 1980-1991 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Non-returning students questionnaire [Partial contents restricted until 2053], 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Northwest Association of Schools and Colleges, 1982-1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Notes from talks: Alumni, 1996-2003 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Notes from talks: Convocation, 1995-2005 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Notes from talks: Family weekend, 1993-2005 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Notes from talks: General, 1998-2009 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - NWCPA [Northwest College Personnel Association], 1985-1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Opening week [Partial contents restricted until 2058], 1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Organizations on campus [memoranda and correspondence], 1979-1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Outing program, 1983-1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Parents Clubs (Portland and Seattle), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Parents Council and newsletter, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Parents Day Hawaiian idea, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Parents handbook, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Parents reception, 1981-1994 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Parents Weekend [schedules, invitations, and planning], 1983-1993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Personal [photographs of Chuck Cleveland, notes on Dean of Students transition], 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Personnel Office, 1982-1993 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Petition [to extend final examinations period], 1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Pioneer (college newspaper), 1984-1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Plagiarism [Folder restricted until 2069], 1980-1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Police [correspondence], 1968-1987 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Police department quarterly campus report, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Pre-College Differential Guidance Battery Instruction Manual, circa 1960 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - President [memoranda and correspondence, search committee] [Partial contents restricted until 2058], 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - President Skotheim's remarks on the retirement of Baker Ferguson from the Board of Trustees, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Presidential inauguration [steering committee materials], 1990 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - [Proposed policy statement] Student exchange program, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Proposed programs for the "Disadvantaged Student", 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Proposed Whitman College Policy on the use of Drugs, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Public service announcement [PSA] posters on alcohol, circa 2004-2015 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Q [correspondence], 1989 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Questionnaire: Part one ETS [Educational Testing Service] on class of 1967 as freshmen [normative data], 1964 January (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Questionnaires [from other colleges and organizations], 1 of 2, 1987-1994 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Questionnaires [from other colleges and organizations], 2 of 2, 1987-1994 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Race symposium [Partial contents restricted until 2081], 2006 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Refunds, 1986-1992 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Registrar, 1980-1994 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Renaissance Faire [schedule and memoranda], 1979-1984 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Retention, 1978-1991 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - S [Sigmi Xi, study abroad, science dinner, summer mailings], 1981-1993 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Scholastic probation [Folder restricted until 2068], 1982-1993 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Security-Safety on campus [Partial contents restricted until 2067], 1987-1992 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Sexual harassment [policy and background information], 1 of 2, 1980-1993 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Sexual harassment [policy and background information], 2 of 2, 1980-1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sexual Harassment - The College's Stand, 2017 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Social norms approach, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Special students [Partial contents restricted until 2067], 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Study on Innovative Practices in Higher Education, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Staff handbook, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Statement on the use of drugs, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Student discipline and grievance [procedures], 1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Student Orientation Acting Revue [SOARing Through Whitman], 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Student petition regarding roll call policy, 1960 February (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Student recognition banquet, 1982-1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Student recognition banquet, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Student recognition banquet, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Student recognition banquet, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - "Statement on AIDS" drafting, information gathering, 1 of 2, 1985-1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - "Statement on AIDS" drafting, information gathering, 2 of 2, 1985-1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - T [suggestions from the student services technology roundtable, town gown award], 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Table Talk, 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Telephones, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Testing, 1978-1992 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Theatre (Harper Joy), 1980-1990 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Tom Goodale visit, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Tower Talk, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Tristram Lundquist memorial scholarship, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Trustees oral report, 1 of 2, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Trustees oral report, 2 of 2, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Trustees oral report, 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Trustees oral report, 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Undergraduate foreign students, 1961-1968 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - V [visiting educators committee], 1980 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Veterans, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Waiilatpu, order of [Folder restricted until 2069], 1967-1994 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - WASC [Western Association of Schools and Colleges], 1991 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - WCHSCR [Washington Council on High School-College Relations] Workshop registration forms, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Washington Pre-College Differential Guidance Program: Manual for the Test Administration, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Washington Pre-College Testing Program: Minutes of the Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1964 July 10 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Washington Pre-College Testing Program: Minutes of the Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1964 November 12 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Washington Pre-College Testing Program: Minutes of the Meeting of the Research Committee, 1965 February 25 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Washington Pre-College Testing Program: Minutes of the Meeting of the Washington Pre-College Testing Committee, 1965 March 26 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Washington Regional Library for the Blind and Physically Handicapped, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Washington State Liquor Control Board ["To Presidents and Deans of Students, All Colleges and Universities in the State of Washington"], 1974 July 12-1974 November 29 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Washington State Penitentiary, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Welcoming lunch for transfer students, invitations to staff, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Whitman College drug policy and correspondence regarding practice, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Whitman in China [program list], circa 1988 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - WISE [Whitman Institute for Science Enrichment] budget, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - W's [withdrawals] from college (possible reversions), 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2042], 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - W's [withdrawals] from college (possible reversions), 2 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2042], 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Wtihdrawal letters [Folder restricted until 2031], 1956 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Wtihdrawal letters [Folder restricted until 2033], 1958 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Wtihdrawal letters [Folder restricted until 2034], 1959 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Wtihdrawal letters [Folder restricted until 2036], 1961 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Wtihdrawal letters, men [Folder restricted until 2035], 1960 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Wtihdrawal letters, women [Folder restricted until 2035], 1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Wtihdrawal letters, men [Folder restricted until 2037], 1963 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Wtihdrawal letters, women [Folder restricted until 2037], 1963 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Withdrawal letters [Folder restricted until 2038], 1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Yearbook, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - YMCA [and YWCA], 1970-1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Fraternities and Sororities, 1963-2005
  - Alpha Chi Omega, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Awards, 1990-1995 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1 of 4 [Folder restricted until 2023], 1985-2003 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 2 of 4 [Folder restricted until 2023], 1985-2003 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 3 of 4 [Folder restricted until 2023], 1985-2003 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 4 of 4 [Folder restricted until 2023], 1985-2003 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Delta Delta Delta [Folder restricted until 2025], 1985-2005 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Delta Gamma [Folder restricted until 2024], 1986-2004 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Delta Tau Delta, 1 of 2, 1986-1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Delta Tau Delta, 2 of 2, 1986-1997 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, and policies, 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2025] [Partial contents restricted until 2080], 1986-2005 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, and policies, 2 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1986-2005 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Housing, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta, 1986-2002 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma [Folder restricted until 2025], 1986-2005 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Memoranda regarding the College Fraternity Secretary Association's "Statement of Position on Hazing and Pre-initiation Activities", 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Memorandum regarding the College Fraternity Secretary Association's "Statement of Position on Hazing and Pre-initiation Activities", 1965-09-01T00:00:00+00:00 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Panhellenic rush, 1 of 2, 1985-2001 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Panhellenic rush, 2 of 2, 1985-2001 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Phi Delta Theta, 1 of 3 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1985-2005 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Phi Delta Theta, 2 of 3 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1985-2005 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Phi Delta Theta, 3 of 3 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1985-2005 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Philosophy and expectations for Greek organizations at Whitman, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Presidents and advisors, 1984-2000 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Rush statistics for all campus Greek organizations, 1967-1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Sigma Chi, 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1985-2005 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Sigma Chi, 2 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1985-2005 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon, 1 of 3 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1985-2005 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon, 2 of 3 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1985-2005 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon, 3 of 3 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1985-2005 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Women's rush stats [fall term], 1965-1969 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Zeta Pi, 1989-1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Housing and Residential Life, 1950-2009
  - Anderson Hall, 1970-2001 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Archives [Memoranda, notices, policies, and orientation materials], 1 of 3, 1950-1974 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Archives [Memoranda, notices, policies, and orientation materials], 2 of 3, 1950-1974 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Archives [Memoranda, notices, policies, and orientation materials], 3 of 3, 1950-1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Co-educational living [transition], 1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Co-educational transition in residence halls, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - College House, 1968-1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Douglas Hall, 1975-1995 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Environmental House, 1990-1999 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Films [campus schedule], 1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Interest house [maintenance, staffing, new houses] 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2029], 1979-2009 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Interest house [maintenance, staffing, new houses] 2 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2029], 1979-2009 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Jewett Hall, 1 of 3, 1969-1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Jewett Hall, 2 of 3, 1969-1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Jewett Hall, 3 of 3, 1969-1999 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Lyman Hall, 1966-1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Marcus House, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Marcus House, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Memorandum regarding the establishment of interest houses, 1967 May (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - North Hall, 1978-1999 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Occupancy, maintenance, policies, and assessments, 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1978-2005 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Occupancy, maintenance, policies, and assessments, 2 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1978-2005 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Occupancy reports: Cars, computers, phones and bikes [Folder restricted until 2025], 1995-2005 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Occupancy reports: Dormitories and fraternity houses [Folder restricted until 2025], 1994-2005 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Petition for co-ed visiting hours, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Prentiss Hall, 1969-1995 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Proposals and applications, surveys, occupancy, and improvements, 1 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2025], 1986-2005 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Proposals and applications, surveys, occupancy, and improvements, 2 of 2 [Folder restricted until 2025] [Partial contents restricted until 2080], 1986-2005 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Residence hall discipline policies, 1977-1982 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Residence hall floor plans, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Housing and residence policy for women, petitions, reports, and questionnaires, 1 of 2, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Housing and residence policy for women, petitions, reports, and questionnaires, 2 of 2, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Staff, 1979-1997 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Staffing, maintenance, and food service [Folder restricted until 2023], 1985-2003 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Student academic advisors, photographs, 1995-2008 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - "Study on Residence Policy for Women," including sample survey and data, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Office of Student Affairs, 1948-2009
  - A Comparative Case Study of Student Services by Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1976 June (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - "A Review of the Student Affairs Program at Whitman College: A report to the President", 1977 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Advising, 1976-1993 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Advising and counseling, 1970 September (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Advising and counseling manuals, 1976-1981 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Advising basics, circa 1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Advising: An Introduction to Advising at Whitman College, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Advising: Lists of advisors and tutors, advising manuals, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Advising: Manual for Freshman Advisors, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Advising: Manual for Freshman Advisors, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Advising: Manual for Freshman Advisors, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Advising: Manual for Freshman Advisors, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Advising: Manual for Freshman Advisors, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Advising: Manual for Freshman Advisors, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Annual report, Associate in Student Affairs, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Annual reports, Associate in Student Affairs, 1 of 2, 1970-1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Annual reports, Associate in Student Affairs, 2 of 2, 1970-1977 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Annual reports, Associate in Student Affairs for Men, 1972-1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Annual report to the faculty, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Annual reports, Office of Student Affairs, 1966-1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - ASWC [Associated Students of Whitman College] bylaws and reports, 1983-1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - ASWC [Associated Students of Whitman College] congress meeting notes, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - ASWC [Associated Students of Whitman College] constitution, 1 of 2, 1971-1986 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - ASWC [Associated Students of Whitman College] constitution, 2 of 2, 1971-1986 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - ASWC [Associated Students of Whitman College] correspondences, 1 of 2, 1982-1993 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - ASWC [Associated Students of Whitman College] correspondences, 2 of 2, 1982-1993 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Calendar of events, 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Campus organization lists, 1972-1979; Office of Student Affairs (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - "Change in titles in Office of Student Affairs," and memorandum concerning start date for academic year, 1964 March-1975 December (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - "Combined Report of Group Scholastic Ratings, First and Second Semesters 1968-69", 1969 June (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - [Contact list] Northwest Council of Guidance and Personnel Associates, circa 1960-1979 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Counseling services, 1 of 2, 1978-1993 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Counseling services, 2 of 2, 1978-1993 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2030], 1953-1955 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2031], 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2032], 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2033], 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2034], 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2035], 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2036], 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2037], 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2038], 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2039], 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2040], 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted untli 2041], 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2042], 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2043], 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2053], 1970-1978 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2071], 1 of 2, 1970 November 4-2004 November 14 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Council on Student Affairs [Folder restricted until 2071], 2 of 2, 1970 November 4-2004 November 14 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Correspondence [Folder restricted until 2043], 1968 (Box 12, Folder 43)